Wow, the weather is so nice.
Timing and subtitles brought to you by
My name is Kota Fukuhara.
I'm a junior in college.
Just like my name implies,
I'm surrounded by lots of happiness every day.
I was born on Strawberry Day, January 5th.
I love strawberry crepes.
I hate bugs and green peppers.
My hobby is exercising,
and I get along with people easily.
I'm looking for love.
I want someone kind and honest.
Or I guess you could say my type is whoever I fall in love with.
Good.
Underclassmen and upperclassmen have different campuses at my school.
So today is my first day at a new campus!
I'm sure I'll meet some great friends
and each day will be more and more rewarding.
After all, just like my name implies...
Look, he stepped in dog poop!
- Poop, poop, poop!
- Don't stare. It's rude.
I'm Kota Fukuhara, a ball of good luck and happiness.
Yeah, as if!
[This introduction was all lies!]
Dropping the sweet act, here's my actual introduction.
It's true I was born on Strawberry Day,
but I'm always the one who gets the bug-infested strawberry.
And...
So sour!
I love beer and fried dumplings.
But even though it's my favorite,
I can't let my guard down.
What I hate is...
kids that always cry,
You're not bleeding.
and train delays.
[Notice: Train Delay]
Oh, shit.
♫ During the day, things aren't looking up and you're discouraged. Yeah! ♫
♫ No matter how tough things may be... You can overcome them, keep it up! ♫
♫  Let's go! I'm right here within your reach ♫
♫ I'll catch you when you fall into despair ♫
♫ I'm here for you. Never leave you ♫
♫ The vast world ♫
♫ could bewilder us from time to time ♫
♫ I hope you'd never change because you're perfect the way you are ♫
[Mr. Unlucky Has No Choice but to Kiss!]
[Episode 1 | Mr. Unlucky Has No Choice but to Kiss!]
My dream is to earn a passive income of 500 million yen.
My ideal type is someone with a nice face.
Your name doesn't change anything.
What the hell?
Stink! What is this?
Contrary to my name,
I've always had unnatural, unreasonable showers of bad luck.
And I've finally come to this conclusion.
I'm just meant to be unlucky.
To prevent my bad luck from spreading,
I don't get close to people.
I act how people expect me to
and pretend to be normal.
That's why I've never gotten close to anyone before.
What happened to you, Fukuhara?
You're drenched.
Oh, this? Don't worry.
It'll dry up soon.
What a breath of fresh air!
Professor Kawahara's psychology class is that way, right?
- Yeah.
- Thanks.
Have you ever asked anyone out before, Shinomiya?
No, I haven't.
Seriously? Have you ever whispered "I love you"
- in someone's ear?
- That would be sweet.
Try it on me.
Try it on me, too.
Psychology. At its core, it's the study of the heart.
[Learning Cube 5]
In that case, how do we define "heart"?
Well...
It's a person's consciousness
as well as their subconscious. Consciousness is...
Professor Kawahara makes no sense, as usual.
I know, right?
Hey, Miki, I love your bracelet.
This? It's beautiful, right?
These rose quartz stones are for luck with romance.
I'm a junior now,
so I bought them from Lord Kirari to find a boyfriend.
Lord Kirari?
He's famous in the spiritual community.
200,000 followers.
This bracelet was purified by Lord Kirari, too.
Amazing, right?
Kirari's "Another Happy Day, Sparkling Kirari!"
Here's the secret of living a happy life surrounded by this sparkling aura.
Calling himself Kirari is amazing in itself.
What? You think so?
Hey, do you smell something?
That smell is probably...
No, it's definitely me.
That bucket of water earlier.
So gross.
- So smelly.
- My shoe.
I made this refreshing, clean image to hide my bad luck, but if I lose that,
what will I do?
[Nit]
- I hope she comes.
- Yeah?
It'd be nice to have a girl there.
Yeah, I know. Right?
Fukuhara, hey there.
You know where tonight's welcome party is, right?
Oh, Izayoi. Right?
I'm going home to change first.
- Oh, okay.
- Yeah, see you.
- See you there.
- See you.
- Bye.
What a refreshing guy.
Yeah.
But did you smell that?
You're imagining things.
- Hold on.
- Naoya and everyone.
What are you doing until the party?
- We're getting some tea. Want to come? Right?
- Yeah.
I have plans.
- It's at Izayoi, right?
- Yeah.
- See you there.
- What?
- Okay.
- Bye.
- See you.
- What? Okay.
That's a shame.
But he's so cool.
What? Don't tell me, Miki.
You want a guy at that level?
Huh? Yeah.
It's fine. I have this with me.
What?
Ugh, a party? What a drag!
Well, it'll be fine if I just make some small talk and bounce.
After all, I...
- Watch out!
- What?
Whoa!
I... I almost died.
- Are you okay?
- Ah!
I... I'm fine.
The guy with a nice face.
Good to hear.
Hurt anywhere? I pulled you pretty hard.
No, I'm okay.
Well, thank you.
- Wait, your hand.
- Oh, this?
I'm really sorry. I can pay or help treat it.
- It's no big deal.
- But...
It only grazed me. It's more important that you're okay.
What's with this attractive guy?
Do people who say that really exist?
At least let me thank you...
Oh, sorry.
Senior? Please stop calling me.
I know.
Izakoi, right?
Okay, see you later.
Wait! Are you...
[Grilled Entrails]
Nice to meet you all.
Juniors, welcome to the Kawahara Seminar.
A word from Professor Kawahara.
- Great!
- Professor!
The study of psychology,
as I said in class today,
- is about learning the heart.
- Professor.
- Yeah?
- It's a welcome party, so don't do that.
- Oh, right.
- Let's make a toast.
Okay, welcome to the Kawahara Seminar. Cheers.
Cheers!
Seniors, please give us your guidance.
- Let's eat.
- Let's eat. Let's dig in.
- Dig in, guys.
- Can I get that for you?
Thanks, Professor.
Oh, boy.
Naoya. Kota. Thanks for joining our seminar.
I got you a cocktail. Is that okay?
Of course. I love cocktails.
That's great.
You look like a cocktail kind of guy.
Oh, you could tell?
I like beer and shochu, you damn idiot.
And what's more...
Those hyenas obviously want my seat,
so they can sit next to Naoya.
But, Naoya, you sure haven't changed.
"Haven't changed"?
You see, I failed German last year,
so I was in his class at the other campus last year.
And the girls I liked were all head over heels for him.
I didn't do anything.
Yeah, I know that.
You super lucky guy.
Super lucky?
Yeah. This guy's overflowing with good luck.
He always wins a good prize in a lottery,
and he can always buy rare tickets.
What?
And vending machines always give him extras.
When I buy vending machine drinks,
extras are the least of my worries.
I don't even get the drink I paid for.
What?
Anyway, whenever he's involved, everything always goes well.
It's just a coincidence.
I'm so jealous.
I'm so envious.
A super lucky guy? What the hell?
Attention, please!
As per seminar tradition,
it's time for the introduction game! You gotta hit exactly one minute!
Seriously?
Okay, who's going to go first?
Let's start with you, Tsujimura.
Come over here.
Come on. Come on.
No way, seriously?
Turn and face everyone.
I don't really know what to say.
Ready?
Okay, begin.
Let me see... I'm Saku Tsujimura.
Um... I've known Naoya and Mugi since high school.
Um... I guess that's it.
Done.
Finished? That was only 13 seconds.
- Okay, I'll go next.
- Oh, no problem.
I'm Mugi Sasaki. I love fashion.
I work part-time at the thrift store near the station, so come visit.
Let's eat, drink, and find girlfriends tonight!
Done.
Close! That was 52 seconds.
My dream is to become a counselor. That's it.
63 seconds.
What?
I'm Naoya Shinomiya. My hobby is exercising.
I do muscle training three times a week.
And I'm a fan of leather clothes, so I collect them.
That's all from me. Thanks for listening.
Wow, that's exactly one minute.
- Amazing!
- For real?
So lucky!
What a super lucky guy!
- Really?
- Look.
You're right.
Please just give me a bit of your luck.
Nice!
And that leaves us with Kota.
Give it to me. This is just unfair.
Fukuhara, come on.
Kota, your turn.
Hey, Kota?
Hey, Kota.
Kota.
It's your turn.
What? Oh, okay.
- What was that?
- Sorry.
I think I'm a bit drunk. I'm sorry.
- Are you ready?
- Yeah.
Okay, our final introduction.
It's all yours, Kota.
Hello, I'm Kota Fukuhara.
My birthday is Strawberry Day, January 5th.
I love strawberry crepes, and I hate...
Let me think...
- What was it?
- What?
Is it a quiz? Wait, let me think.
Never mind, I'm done now.
Too bad. It was 29 seconds.
Okay, and that concludes
our exactly one-minute self-introduction game. Thanks, everyone.
Good work.
What?
Is beer okay?
Oh... yes.
Thanks.
How did he know I wanted beer?
Well, I guess I can tell he's a good guy.
And tonight...
I had such a good time!
The waiter never spilled water on me
and no one threw up on me.
Ah, I smell so nice. This is Heaven.
Could it be?
Is my bad luck...
Of course, I still got it.
You've been following me, haven't you? Stalker!
Ouch.
But still...
Why so suddenly?
Could it be?
It wouldn't be unusual for me to break a bone there.
And tonight's party, too...
Beer is so good.
You're cute.
I'd usually get alcohol, soy sauce, or vomit on me
and have to go through hell.
You're seriously cute.
Could it be?
Was my bad luck repelled
by that guy?
Naoya, can I get your number?
Yeah, sure.
- Really?
- Me, too.
- Do you want mine, too?
- No, thanks.
Don't be shy.
- You don't want it?
- I'm so happy.
Hey...
Oh, it's Kota.
Can I talk to Naoya for a second?
- Naoya?
- Sure.
Sorry, excuse me.
Hey, come back soon. Okay?
Sorry.
Bye-bye.
That was crazy back there.
Thanks for the help.
So, what is it?
Well, the only person I know on this campus is you,
so I was wondering if we could tour the place together.
Oh, that's it?
Sure thing.
Really? I'm so glad.
Where should we go?
I got you now, my attractive Naoya.
I'll investigate how well you annul my bad luck today.
How about the cafeteria?
Sure. I was actually getting a bit hungry.
Let's go.
[Recruiting Members| Remote Control Society]
What is that?
I wasn't hit? Good luck already?
You like remote control toys?
Not at all.
- Let's go.
- Okay.
No, it's still too early to tell.
Wow.
My chopsticks broke evenly.
My noodles are usually cold and soggy.
They've never tasted so good before.
This coffee's great, too.
Darn, this is so heavy.
You like coffee, too?
- Yeah.
- Oh, no.
It's going to spill.
Gosh, he's definitely coming my way.
I'll help you.
- Thanks.
- Not at all.
Thanks.
I didn't get splashed?
Hey, this looks interesting.
It didn't hit me.
Where to go next?
What do I do?
It turned out amazing. Thanks!
What? She's not mad!
It's amazing!
Where should we go next?
Yeah, let's see...
- Whoa!
- Kota!
I didn't fall!
Amazing! Amazing!
This is great!
Huh? What?
Sorry.
I've been keeping it in,
but Kota, your eyes are shining.
Oops.
But... this was really fun.
You're pretty cute.
Like a puppy.
A... A puppy?
I'm not.
What a formidable guy.
Anyone would fall for him after hearing such words from that face.
He doesn't know he's a lady-killer.
This is dangerous.
If I hang with him,
there's going to be a blood bath eventually.
What?
No, it's nothing.
Let's go.
Sure.
But it's hard to give up his effect on my bad luck.
Um... Naoya.
Naoya, I have something else I want to talk about.
Okay.
If I want to use this guy and his good luck,
I'll have to...
I was hoping we could stay together always.
No?
Wait, did I mess up?
Sure.
What?
Okay, let's stay together.
All right!
Really? Thanks...
What?
Just now...
Couples normally kiss, right?
What?
Now we're dating.
What?! That's not what I meant though!
Timing and subtitles brought to you by
♫ Let's go on this path ♫
♫ Together while holding hands ♫
♫ Let's get to know each other ♫
♫ entirely till the day we die ♫
[PREVIEW]
Who's dating Naoya?
Let's go together.
Naoya and I...
Then we can be together all day.
Naoya!
I can't let my partner catch a cold.
I'm really sorry.
It was my fault.
[THIS DRAMA IS A WORK OF FICTION.]